Joan McBreen papers
Emory University
- Photographs, 1979-2000, Series 6; Boxes 35-36
  - Ní Chuilleanáine, Eiléan, April 24, 1999 (Box 36, Folder 32)
  - Ní Dhomhnaill, Nuala (Box 36, Folder 33)
  - Ní Dhomhalláin, Máirín, May 20, 1999 (Box 36, Folder 34)
  - Ní Ghallehóir, Colette, February 26, 1999 (Box 36, Folder 35)
  - Ní Ghlinn, Áine (Box 36, Folder 36)
  - O'Callaghan, Julie, March 23, 1999 (Box 36, Folder 37)
  - O'Connor, Clairr (Box 36, Folder 38)
  - O'Donnell, Mary (Box 36, Folder 39)
  - O'Driscoll, Kathleen, September 11, 1999 (Box 36, Folder 40)
  - O'Hagan, Shelia, June 16, 1999 (Box 36, Folder 41)
  - O'Mahoney, Nessa (Box 36, Folder 42)
  - O'Malley, Mary (Box 36, Folder 43)
  - Parkinson, Barbara, March 4, 1999 (Box 36, Folder 44)
  - Paterson, Evangeline, March 9, 1999 (Box 36, Folder 45)
  - Patton, Angela (Box 36, Folder 46)
  - Rowley, Rosemarie, circa 1954 (Box 36, Folder 47)
  - Shanahan, Diedre, February 25, 1999 (Box 36, Folder 48)
  - Shepperson, Janet, March 3, 1999 (Box 36, Folder 49)
  - Slade, Jo (Box 36, Folder 50)
  - Sullivan, Breda (Box 36, Folder 51)
  - Taylor, Alice, March 4, 1999 (Box 36, Folder 52)
  - Thurley, Judith, April 22, 1999 (Box 36, Folder 53)
  - Uí Fhoghlu, Áine (Box 36, Folder 54)
  - Uí Nuanáin, Máire, May 20, 1999 (Box 36, Folder 55)
  - Valentine, Jean (Box 36, Folder 56)
  - Vial, Noelle, June 1996 (Box 36, Folder 57)
  - Warke, Oonagh, September 14, 1999 (Box 36, Folder 58)
  - Wichert, Sabine, March 4, 1999 (Box 36, Folder 59)
  - Wyley, Enda, 1998 (Box 36, Folder 60)
- Audiovisual, 1988-1995, Series 7; Box 37
  This series contains sound recordings collected by McBreen and consist primarily of recordings of her friend, poet Anne Kennedy, from 1988-1995.
  - Sound recordings - Cassettes
  - "Thought for the Day," featuring Anne Kennedy, August 1988 (Box 37)
  - Buck Mountain Poems, reading by Anne Kennedy, December 27, 1988 (Box 37)
  - "A Paperback Programme," featuring Anne Kennedy discussing Anton Chekhov, February 10, 1990 (Box 37)
  - "Scenes from a Return Journey," Anne Kennedy and Julian Vignoles, RTE I, September 19, 1992 (Box 37)
  - "Martha and Mary," Anne Kennedy and John McKenna, RTE I, December 1, 1992 (Box 37)
  - Eavan Boland interview, RTE I, April 13, 1994 [side A] (Box 37)
  - Anne Kennedy reading, Cúirt International Festival of Literature, 1994 [side B] (Box 37)
  - "Where I Live, What I Live For," Anne Kennedy reading with John McKenna, RTE I, December 12, 1994 (Box 37)
  - "Down in Yonder Forest," Anne Kennedy reading with John McKenna, RTE I, December 17, 1994 (Box 37)
  - Anne Kennedy with Jim Carney, Galway Bay, December 26, 1995 (Box 37)
- Born digital material, 1993-1999, Series 8; Box 38
  Restrictions on Access
  Special restrictions apply: born digital materials are restricted from use.
  - 3 1/2" Floppy disks
  - "Joan McBreen," June 10, 1999 (Box 38)
  - "The Ripple Tank Experience (Poems by Jean Bleakney)" (Box 38)
  - "Winter in the Eye" (Box 38)
  - "a: \women.bio" December 15, 1993 (Box 38)
  - "a: \women.bio, biographies" (Box 38)